{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Seismic/Earthquake Retrofitters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40215/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40215,"taskName":"Earthquake Protection - Retrofit","taskDescription":"Earthquake-Proof a Structure","xmTaskDescriptor":"Seismic/Earthquake Retrofitters","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1503,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Earthquake Protection damage recovery protect","textMessagingName":"Retrofit Quake","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms specialize in the design \u0026 implementation of plans to make existing structures better able to survive the destructive forces of an earthquake. Typically also expert in earthquake resistant building codes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Retrofit a structure to make it earthquake resistant.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Earthquake-Proof a Structure.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Seismic Retrofit \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Earthquake Retrofitting \u0026 Protection","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":53,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Earthquake Protection Retrofit","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Earthquake Protection - Retrofit","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Earthquake Protection Retrofitter Need","urlName":"Earthquake-Protection-Retrofit","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Seismic Retrofit Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Earthquake,Protection,damage,recovery,protect,preare,preparedness,Retrofit","emcCategoryOid":-12022,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":522,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40215/":{"taskOID":40215,"originalTaskOID":40215,"setID":522,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4684,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Assessment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":870,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","answerDisplayText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Development of a set of plans","answerDisplayText":"Development of a set of plans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","answerDisplayText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4686,"questionDisplayText":"Home Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following describes your home? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Two or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6203,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","answerDisplayText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","answerDisplayText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3047,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home has an unusual shape","answerDisplayText":"Home has an unusual shape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6562,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","answerDisplayText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5956,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Split level","answerDisplayText":"Split level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4808,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","answerDisplayText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","answerDisplayText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3050,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home is on a steep hill","answerDisplayText":"Home is on a steep hill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4684,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Assessment","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What services do you need? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":870,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","answerDisplayText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Development of a set of plans","answerDisplayText":"Development of a set of plans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","answerDisplayText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":870,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","answerDisplayText":"Assessment of what needs to be retrofitted","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1905,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Development of a set of plans","answerDisplayText":"Development of a set of plans","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5900,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","answerDisplayText":"Someone to perform the retrofit work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4686,"questionDisplayText":"Home Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which of the following describes your home? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Two or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6203,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","answerDisplayText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","answerDisplayText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3047,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home has an unusual shape","answerDisplayText":"Home has an unusual shape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6562,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","answerDisplayText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5956,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Split level","answerDisplayText":"Split level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4808,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","answerDisplayText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","answerDisplayText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3050,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home is on a steep hill","answerDisplayText":"Home is on a steep hill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6553,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Two or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6203,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","answerDisplayText":"Supported by posts, not a wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2603,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","answerDisplayText":"Foundation is brick or is weak","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3047,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home has an unusual shape","answerDisplayText":"Home has an unusual shape","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6562,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","answerDisplayText":"Two-car or larger garage with rooms above it","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5956,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Split level","answerDisplayText":"Split level","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4808,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","answerDisplayText":"Porch that is recessed beneath a second story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3049,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","answerDisplayText":"Home is almost touching an adjacent home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3050,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Home is on a steep hill","answerDisplayText":"Home is on a steep hill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":9,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}